Guide to the Bank of Willows Records, 1880-1905 JL013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Bank of Willows Records,
1880-1905
JL013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
6.0 Linear feet
Bank of Willows
Scope and Content
The collection consists of volumes of the Bank of Willows, a town (county seat) in Glenn County, California. The record books cover the years 1880-1905 and include journals (1890-1902); cash books (1880-1890); ledger (1880-1887); bills receivable register and bill books (1886-1905), as well as check and voucher records.
Provenance
Transferred from the Jackson Library of Business, 1979.
Access Restrictions
None.
- Journal, 1890-1893 (Volume 1)
- Journal, 1896-1899 (Volume 2)
- Journal, 1899-1902 (Volume 3)
- Cash book, 1880-1881 (Volume 4)
- Cash book, 1882-1883 (Volume 5)
- Cash book, 1885-1887 (Volume 6)
- Cash book, 1887-1889 (Volume 7)
- Cash book, 1889-1890 (Volume 8)
- Ledger, 1880-1887 (Volume 9)
- Bills receivable register, 1886-1889 (Volume 10)
- Bill book, 1887-1892 (Volume 11)
- Bill book, 1897-1905 (Volume 12)
- Check register, 1881-1886 (Volume 13)
- Voucher record, 1904-1907 (Volume 14)
- Profit and loss book, 1889-1890 (Volume 15)